<productListing title = "My Books">
    
        <book1>
            <name>12 Rules For Life</name>
            <author>Jordan B Peterson</author>
            <publicationdate>January 16, 2018</publicationdate>
            <description>An Antidote to Chaos is a 2018 self-help book by Canadian clinical psychologist 
                    and psychology professor Jordan Peterson. It provides life advice through essays in abstract ethical principles,
                    psychology, mythology, religion, and personal anecdotes.</description>
            <publishername>Random House Canada Penguin Allen Lane (UK)</publishername>
            <language>english</language>
            <isbnnumber>9780141988511</isbnnumber>
            <quote>
                <quote1>Treat yourself like you are someone you are responsible for helping</quote1>
                <quote2>Make friends with people who want the best for you</quote2>
                <quote3>Set your house in perfect order before you criticize the world</quote3>
            </quote>
            <bookid>BUK00001</bookid>
        </book1>
        <book2>
            <name>The 48 Laws of Power</name>
            <author>Robert Greene</author>
            <publicationdate>1998</publicationdate>
            <description>The 48 Laws of Power is a non-fiction book, self-help book. And is popular with prison inmates and celebrities.</description>
            <publishername>Penguin Books</publishername>
            <language>english</language>
            <isbnnumber>0-670-88146-5</isbnnumber>
            <quote>
                <quote1>Lord, protect me from my friends; I can take care of my enemies.</quote1>
                <quote2>There is nothing more intoxicating than victory, and nothing more dangerous.</quote2>
                <quote3>Strike the shepherd and the sheep will scatter</quote3>
            </quote>
            <bookid>BUK00002</bookid>
        </book2>
        <book3>
            <name>Nineteen Eighty-Four</name>
            <author>George Orwell</author>
            <publicationdate>1949</publicationdate>
            <description>Nineteen Eighty-Four has become a classic literary example of political and dystopian fiction. 
                    The story takes place in an imagined future, the year 1984, when much of the world has fallen victim to perpetual war, 
                    omnipresent government surveillance, historical negationism, and propaganda.</description>
            <publishername>Secker and Warburg</publishername>
            <language>english</language>
            <isbnnumber>9780141391700</isbnnumber>
            <quote>
                <quote1>We shall meet in the place where there is no darkness.</quote1>
                <quote2>If you loved someone, you loved him, and when you had nothing else to give,you still gave him love.</quote2>
                <quote3>It's a beautiful thing, the destruction of words.</quote3>
            </quote>
            <bookid>BUK00003</bookid>
        </book3>
    
</productListing>